<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.kleopatra.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Kleopatra</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Kleopatra</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Kleopatra</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Kleopatra</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Kleopatra</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Kleopatra</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Kleopatra</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Kleopatra</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">Kleopatra</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">Kleopatra</name>
  <name xml:lang="nb">Kleopatra</name>
  <name xml:lang="nds">Kleopatra</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Kleopatra</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Kleopatra</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Kleopatra</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Kleopatra</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">Kleopatra</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Kleopatra</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Kleopatra</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Kleopatra</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Kleopatra</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKleopatraxx</name>
  <summary>Certificate Manager and Unified Crypto GUI</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Gestor de certificats i interfície gràfica d'usuari de criptografia unificada</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Správce certifikátů a rozhraní pro šifrování</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Zertifikatsverwaltung und einheitliche Oberfläche für Kryptografie</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Certificate Manager and Unified Crypto GUI</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Gestor de certificados e interfaz gráfica unificada de cifrado</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Varmenteiden hallinta ja yhtenäinen salauskäyttöliittymä</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Gestionnaire de certificats et interface utilisateur unifiée pour le chiffrement</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Tanúsítványkezelő és egységes kriptográfiai kezelőfelület</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">인증서 관리자와 통합된 암호화 GUI</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nb">Sertifikatbehandler og forent krypto-GUI</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nds">Zertifikatenpleger un eenheitlich Verslötel-Böversiet</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Certificaatbeheerder en Unified Crypto GUI</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Zarządzanie certyfikatami i kryptografią</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Gestor de Certificados e GUI Unificada de Criptografia</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Gerenciador de certificados e interface gráfica de criptografia unificada</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Správca certifikátov a unifikované šifrovacie grafické rozhranie</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Upravljalnik potrdil in enoten šifrirni vmesnik</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Certifikathanterare och enhetligt grafiskt användargränssnitt för krypto</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Графічний інтерфейс до засобів керування сертифікатами та універсальних можливостей з шифрування.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxCertificate Manager and Unified Crypto GUIxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Kleopatra is a certificate manager and a universal crypto GUI.
      It supports managing X.509 and OpenPGP certificates in the GpgSM keybox and retrieving certificates from LDAP servers.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Kleopatra és un gestor de certificats i interfície gràfica d'usuari de criptografia universal. Implementa la gestió dels certificats X.509 i OpenPGP a l'anell de claus GpgSM i recupera certificats des de servidors LDAP.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Kleopatra is a certificate manager and a universal crypto GUI. It supports managing X.509 and OpenPGP certificates in the GpgSM keybox and retrieving certificates from LDAP servers.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Kleopatra es un gestor de certificados e interfaz gráfica universal de cifrado. Reconoce certificados X.509 y OpenPGP en el llavero GpgSM y la recuperación de certificados desde servidores LDAP.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Kleopatra on varmenteiden hallinta ja yhtenäinen salauskäyttöliittymä. Se tukee X.509- ja OpenPGP-varmenteiden hallintaa GpgSM-avainlaatikossa ja varmenteiden noutoa LDAP-palvelimilta.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A Kleopatra egy tanúsítványkezelő és egységes kriptográfiai kezelőfelület. Támogatja az X.509-es és OpenPGP tanúsítványok kezelését a GpgSM kulcsdobozban és tanúsítványok letöltését LDAP kiszolgálókról.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">Kleopatra는 인증서 관리자와 통합된 범용 암호화 GUI입니다. GpgSM 키 상자에 저장된 X.509 및 OpenPGP 인증서를 관리하고, LDAP 서버에서 인증서를 가져올 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nb">Kleopatra er en sertifikatbehandler og en universal krypto-brukerflate. Den har støtte for å behandle X.509 og OpenPGP-sertifikater i nøkkelboksen CpgSM, og henter sertifikater fra LDP-tjenere.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nds">Kleopatra is en Zertifikatenpleger un en Böversiet för Verslötelakschonen. Du kannst dor X.509- un OpenPGP-Zertifikaten mit binnen de GpgSM-Slötelkist plegen un Zertifikaten mit vun LDAP-Servers halen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Kleopatra is een certificaatbeheerder en een universele crypto GUI. Deze ondersteunt het beheer van X.509 en OpenPGP certificaten in de GpgSM sleutelkast en haalt certificaten op van LDAP-servers.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Kleopatra jest programem do zarządzania certyfikatami i uniwersalnym układem sterowania kryptografią. Obsługuje zarządzanie certyfikatami X.509 oraz OpenPGP w skrzynce na klucze GpgSM oraz pobieranie certyfikatów z serwerów LDAP.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Kleopatra é um gestor de certificados e uma interface de cifra universal. Suporta a gestão de certificados X.509 e do OpenPGP no porta-chaves do GpgSM e a obtenção dos certificados a partir de servidores de LDAP.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Kleopatra é um gerenciador de certificados e uma interface de criptografia universal. Tem suporte a gerenciamento de certificados X.509 e OpenPGP no porta-chaves do GpgSM e obtenção de certificados a partir de servidores LDAP.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Kleopatra je správca certifikátov a univerzálne šifrovacie GUI. Podporuje správu X.509 a OpenPGP certifikátov v keyboxe GpgSM a získavanie certifikátov z LDAP serverov.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Kleopatra je upravljalnik potrdil in enoten šifrirni vmesnik. Podpira rokovanje s potrdili X.509 in OpenPGP v zbirki ključev GpgSM in omogoča pridobivanje potrdil iz strežnikov LDAP.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Kleopatra är en certifikathanterare och ett universellt grafiskt användargränssnitt för krypto. Den stöder hantering av X.509- och OpenPGP-certifikat i GpgSM-nyckellådan och att hämta certifikat från LDAP-servrar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Kleopatra — графічний інтерфейс засобів керування сертифікатами та шифрування. У програмі передбачено можливості з керування сертифікатами X.509 та OpenPGP у сховищі ключів GpgSM та отримання сертифікатів з серверів LDAP.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKleopatra is a certificate manager and a universal crypto GUI. It supports managing X.509 and OpenPGP certificates in the GpgSM keybox and retrieving certificates from LDAP servers.xx</p>
  </description>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kleopatra</url>
  <url type="help">http://docs.kde.org/stable/en/kdepim/kleopatra/index.html</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://kde.org/images/screenshots/kleopatra.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>kleopatra</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
