<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>kleopatra.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Kleopatra</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Kleopatra</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Kleopatra</name>
  <name xml:lang="nds">Kleopatra</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Kleopatra</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Kleopatra</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Kleopatra</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Kleopatra</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKleopatraxx</name>
  <summary>Certificate Manager and Unified Crypto GUI</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Gestor de certificats i interfície gràfica d'usuari de criptografia unificada</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Správce certifikátů a rozhraní pro šifrování</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nds">Zertifikatenpleger un eenheitlich Verslötel-Böversiet</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Certificaatbeheerder en Unified Crypto GUI</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Správca certifikátov a unifikované šifrovacie grafické rozhranie</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Certifikathanterare och enhetligt grafiskt användargränssnitt för krypto</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Графічний інтерфейс до засобів керування сертифікатами та універсальних можливостей з шифрування.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxCertificate Manager and Unified Crypto GUIxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Kleopatra is a certificate manager and a universal crypto GUI.
      It supports managing X.509 and OpenPGP certificates in the GpgSM keybox and retrieving certificates from LDAP servers.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Kleopatra és un gestor de certificats i interfície gràfica d'usuari de criptografia universal. Implementa la gestió dels certificats X.509 i OpenPGP a l'anell de claus GpgSM i recupera certificats des de servidors LDAP.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nds">Kleopatra is en Zertifikatenpleger un en Böversiet för Verslötelakschonen. Du kannst dor X.509- un OpenPGP-Zertifikaten mit binnen de GpgSM-Slötelkist plegen un Zertifikaten mit vun LDAP-Servers halen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Kleopatra is een certificaatbeheerder en een universele crypto GUI. Deze ondersteunt het beheer van X.509 en OpenPGP certificaten in de GpgSM sleutelkast en haalt certificaten op van LDAP-servers.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Kleopatra je správca certifikátov a univerzálne šifrovacie GUI. Podporuje správu X.509 a OpenPGP certifikátov v keyboxe GpgSM a získavanie certifikátov z LDAP serverov.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Kleopatra är en certifikathanterare och ett universellt grafiskt användargränssnitt för krypto. Den stöder hantering av X.509- och OpenPGP-certifikat i GpgSM-nyckellådan och att hämta certifikat från LDAP-servrar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Kleopatra — графічний інтерфейс засобів керування сертифікатами та шифрування. У програмі передбачено можливості з керування сертифікатами X.509 та OpenPGP у сховищі ключів GpgSM та отримання сертифікатів з серверів LDAP.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKleopatra is a certificate manager and a universal crypto GUI. It supports managing X.509 and OpenPGP certificates in the GpgSM keybox and retrieving certificates from LDAP servers.xx</p>
  </description>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kleopatra</url>
  <url type="help">http://docs.kde.org/stable/en/kdepim/kleopatra/index.html</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://kde.org/images/screenshots/kleopatra.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>kleopatra</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
