<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>kaddressbook.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>KAddressBook</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KAddressBook</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">KAddressBook</name>
  <name xml:lang="nds">KAdressbook</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KAddressBook</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KAddressBook</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Adressbok</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KAddressBook</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKAddressBookxx</name>
  <description>
    <p>KAddressBook stores all the personal details of your family, friends and other contacts.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KAddressBook emmagatzema totes les dades personals de la vostra família, amics i altres contactes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nds">KAdressbook wohrt all de persöönlichen Enkelheiten över Dien Familie, Dien Frünnen un anner Kontakten.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KAddressBook slaat alle persoonlijke details op van uw familie, vrienden en andere contactpersonen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Adressboken lagrar all personlig information för din familj, dina vänner och andra kontakter.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Програма KAddressBook здатна зберігати особисті дані для спілкування з вашою родиною, друзями та дані щодо контактів.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKAddressBook stores all the personal details of your family, friends and other contacts.xx</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Vlastnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nds">Markmalen:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Mogelijkheden:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Funkcie:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Можливості:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Imports and exports to nearly every address book standard</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Importa i exporta a gairebé tots els estàndards de la llibreta d'adreces</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Importeren ut un Exporteren na meist all Adressbook-Standards.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Importeert en exporteert naar bijna elke adresboekstandaard</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Importerar och exporterar till nästan alla adressboksstandarder</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">імпортування та експортування даних у майже довільних стандартах зберігання даних адресних книг;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxImports and exports to nearly every address book standardxx</li>
      <li>Reads .vcf format files, and can import and export vCards and csv format files</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Llegeix el format de fitxer .vcf, i pot importar i exportar els formats de fitxer vCard i CSV</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Leest Dateien in't VCF-Formaat un kann Daten ut vCard- un CSV-Dateien importeren un dor ok hen exporteren.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Leest .vcf-formaat bestanden en kan vCards importeren en exporteren en csv-formaat bestanden</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Läser filer med .vcf-format, och kan importera och exportera filer med vCard- och csv-format</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">читання файлів у форматі .vcf, імпортування та експортування даних у форматах vCard та CSV;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxReads .vcf format files, and can import and export vCards and csv format filesxx</li>
      <li>Can use multiple LDAPservers</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Pot usar múltiples servidors LDAP</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Kann en Reeg LDAP-Servers tosamen bruken</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Kan meerdere LDAP-servers gebruiken</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Kan använda flera LDAP-servrar</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">можливість використання декількох серверів LDAP;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxCan use multiple LDAPserversxx</li>
      <li>Configurable filters and powerful search capabilities</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Filtres configurables i potents capacitats de cerca</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Instellbor Filtern un en deegt Söök</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">In te stellen filters en krachtige zoekfuncties</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Inställningsbara filter och kraftfulla sökmöjligheter</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">зручні фільтри та потужні можливості з пошуку;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxConfigurable filters and powerful search capabilitiesxx</li>
      <li>Integrates with other Kontact components, e.g. exporting Birthday reminders to KOrganizer</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">S'integra amb els altres components del Kontact, p. ex., l'exportació dels recordatoris d'aniversari pel KOrganizer</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Arbeit mit anner Kontact-Komponenten tosamen, exporteert a.B. Geboortsdag-Vöranstööt na KOrganizer.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Integreert met andere componenten van Kontact, bijv. exporteren van herinneringen van verjaardagen aan KOrganizer</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Integrerar med andra komponenter i Kontact, t.ex. med export av påminnelser om födelsedagar till Korganizer</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">інтеграція з іншими компонентами Kontact, зокрема експортування нагадувань щодо днів народження до KOrganizer;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxIntegrates with other Kontact components, e.g. exporting Birthday reminders to KOrganizerxx</li>
      <li>Capable of groupware integration</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Capaç d'integrar-se amb el treball en grup</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Arbeit mit Arbeitkoppelprogrammen tosamen</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Kan met groupware integreren</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Klarar av integrering med grupprogram</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">можливість інтегрування з програмним забезпеченням для групової роботи;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxCapable of groupware integrationxx</li>
      <li>Powered by Akonadi</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Desenvolupat per a l'Akonadi</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Akonadi arbeidt in'n Achtergrund</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Powered door Akonadi</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Drivs av Akonadi</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">усі додаткові можливості, роботу яких забезпечує Akonadi.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxPowered by Akonadixx</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kaddressbook</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://kde.org/images/screenshots/kaddressbook.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>kaddressbook</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
